I.) General Information

	1.) Folder order should resemble the real-world build order as close as possible, whilst focusing on the most important areas.

		Subfolders should be lettered A-Z, as illustrated below:

			[A] Structural Supports
			[B] Front Idler
			[C] Top Idler
			[D] Rear Idler
			[F] Track Tensioner
			[G] Battery Boxes
			[H] Idler Gear
			[I] Track

		However, in the case of the topmost areas, we have:

			[00 FULL] Complete Assembly
			[01 HEAD] Head
			[02 NECK] Neck
			[03 SHDR] Shoulder
			[04 ARM] Arms
			...
			...
			[16 HDWR] Hardware
			[17 ELEC] Electronics
		
	    This would better represent the robot, from completed down to its lowest components used throughout. The preceding numbers are simply used as placeholders to keep the areas in order.

	2.) All files inherit their top-level folders' bracket information.

	3.) Part numbers start with "00" and end at "99". This allows for 100 parts, but there should never be more than 100 parts in a single folder. That could be called clutter and poor organization.
	    The renaming program will work fine beyond 100 parts, however it will notify you when the situation arises.

	4.) Assemblies do not have part numbers, as they are a collection of parts and adding more numbers could be confusing.

	5.) Assemblies should be in the topmost area folder as often as possible.

		Example: "J5 Project CAD 2014\[02 NECK] Neck\[NECK] Neck Assembly.SLDASM"

		This allows for easy access to the completed neck. This will result in ease of construction for the full robot assembly. There are some cases where this may not be possible due to the way
		our assemblies are built.

	6.) Assemblies should not use the word "Assembly" within as much as possible. The word "Assembly" should only be used if a filename is not descriptive enough, or if it could be confused with
	    a part of a similar name. Another reason is that we do not add the word "Part" to all parts, because that would be plain silly; that's what the file extension (.SLDPRT/.SLDASM) is there for.

		Example:
			"[TDRV-COMN-H] Track Assembly.SLDASM" 
			"[TDRV-COMN-C] Rear Idler.SLDASM"

		The word "Track" by itself could be easily confused with the track drive or a track link. The title "Track Assembly" infers a collection of whatever a "track" is.
		However, "Rear Idler" is descriptive enough, and is not a title used often.

	7.) All important letters in a name must be capital. General rule of thumb is to name as if you were naming a file following book or song title rules. A filename is a short description -- not a
	    sentence -- thus it would look strange to only capitalize the first letter.

	8.) There is no limit to filename length aside from any imposed by Windows, though it should be as short as humanly possible.

		Example: "[ELEC-MOTR-A28400-COMN-01] Shaft.SLDPRT" located in the "[A28400] AmpFlow A28-400" folder

		We know that this part is related to the AmpFlow A28-400 from both the "prefix" and above folder name. Thus, it would be silly and cluttered to name the file "AmpFlow A28-400 Shaft" as
		opposed to the much simpler and intuitive "Shaft".

	9.) Individual folder prefixes must never contain dashes. 

		Example:
			A folder named "[EYE-LEFT]"
			A folder named "[FINGER-RIGHT]"
			A folder named "[BDPG-60-110]"
	
	10.) If a part has a part number through McMaster-Carr, it is placed in parentheses and prefixed by "MCMC". Other manufacturer part numbers can be included in parenthesis. In some cases, it would
	     be optimal to not put the part number in parentheses. If a part number is unknown, it must be stated. Ideally, ALL purchased parts -- or derivatives of purchased parts --- should have a
	     manufacturer part number included.

		Example:
			"[HDWR-BRNG-NDL] 0.375 x 0.5625 x 0.5 (MCMC 5905K22).SLDPRT"
			"[HDWR-BRNG-BALL-US-S] 0.75 x 40mm x 12mm (6203-2RS-12).SLDPRT"
			"[HRDW-GEAR] Uni-Chains 29-Tooth Sprocket (123381529N).SLDPRT"
			"[HDWR-BRNG-TAPR] 0.5 x 0.377 x 0.47 (Unknown).SLDPRT"
			"[ELEC-MOTR-BDPG60110] Anaheim Automation BDPG-60-110-24V-3000-R76.SLDASM"

			In the first, second, and third examples, we see it would be worthwhile to put the manufacturer part number in parentheses.

			In the fourth example, we clearly see the part number is unknown and must be researched further, or replaced.

			In the last example, should "BDPG-60-110-24V-3000-R76" be in parentheses, how is one to know what an "Anaheim Automation" is? Basically, a part should be read mentally without parenthesis.

	11.) Windows does not allow the use of slashes in filenames. To get around this limitation, we are using a character that looks similar to a forward slash, but it is not.
	     / - U+002F Solidus (ie. Forward Slash)
	     ̸  - U+0338 Combining Long Solidus Overlay
	     The easiest way to use it is to simply copy this character from a filename that already has it. Many of our fasteners and bearings have a slash in their filenames.

		Example A:
			"[HDWR-BRNG-BALL-UK-S] 22 x 44 x 12 (60̸ 22-2RS).SLDPRT"

			This is an excellent case. The part number is "60/22-2RS". However, there is another bearing that exists called "6022-2RS", and it has vastly different dimensions. Not including the slash
			or using a hypen could lead to confusion, and in the worst case, an incorrect purchase! Do note: a real forward slash should always be used in the SolidWorks part description/properties.

		Example B:
			"[HDWR-BRNG-BALL-US-S] 1-1̸ 4 x 2-1̸ 4 x 1̸ 2 (R20-2RS).SLDPRT"

			This is far easier to read and interpret than "[HDWR-BRNG-BALL-US-S] 1 1-4 x 2 1-4 x 1-2 (R20-2RS).SLDPRT" or "[HDWR-BRNG-BALL-US-S] 1.25 x 2.25 x 0.5 (R20-2RS).SLDPRT".

		Example C:
			"[HDWR-BRNG-TAPR] 1̸ 2 x 1.377 x 0.47 (A4050 & A4138).SLDPRT"

			In this case, it would be advantageous to use decimals (where applicable) for this part. Even though "1.377" is very close to 1-3/8, NEVER round numbers.

	12.) If a part can be further defined, it should be placed in parentheses. Also, if the name is the same, it would be wise to keep the part number the same as well, as shown below.

		Example:
			"[TDRV-COVR-01-L] Side Shield Plate (Left).SLDPRT"
			"[TDRV-COVR-01-R] Side Shield Plate (Right).SLDPRT"
			"[TDRV-COMN-G-COMN-00-MALE] Shaft (Male).SLDPRT"
			"[TDRV-COMN-G-COMN-00-FEML] Shaft (Female).SLDPRT"

			We can ascertain that the side shield plate is a mirrored part, having a left and right version. We can also see that the two shaft parts connect, as they are male and female.
			This simplifies part numbering and makes the "prefix" more descriptive.
			
			The renaming program will currently take notice of these items in parentheses, and apply them to the "prefix" in the same manner the examples above are displayed.

			(Front) = FRNT
			(Rear) = REAR
			(Left) = L
			(Right) = R
			(Left-Handed) = LH
			(Right-Handed) = RH
			(Upper) = UPR
			(Lower) = LWR
			(Inner) = INNR
			(Outer) = OUTR
			(Long) = LONG
			(Short) = SHRT
			(Female) = FEML
			(Male) = MALE
			(Sprocket) = SPKT

			Comma-delimited items such as "(Left, Inner)" or "(Short, Male)" are currently not taken into account.

----------

II.) Common Folders

	"Common" folders are always "[00 COMN]". The "00" is purely visual; it keeps the folder at the top of Windows Explorer so that this extremely vital folder will not get lost among other folders.
	The best definition of a Common folder would be "Shared between one or more entities."

	For example, the track drive top idler has a ten-inch circular disc, and said disc is not used anywhere else within the track drive.
	Thus, creating a Common folder within the same folder as the top idler assembly, and placing the ten-inch disc inside would be ideal.
	Also, because the top idler is a shared entity -- used within both the left and right units -- the top idler assembly should go in a Common folder, as well.

		Example: "[TDRV-COMN-E-COMN-01] Tension Adjustment Washer.SLDPRT"

		From this example, we can deduce that this is a track drive part. It is used between both the left and right track drives, and is used within assembly "E".

----------

III.) Coverings

	Coverings should be placed in a folder named "[01 COVR]", and always be in the top area folder. This keeps the folder below [00 COMN], and allows easy searching for a covering.
	The reason the covering folder should be below the Common folder, is that not all areas have coverings. However many, if not ALL areas have Common parts.
	However, if in rare occasion, a Common folder does not need to exist for an area, it may be allowable to have "[00 COVR]".

		Example: "[TDRV-COVR-02-R] Accessory Covering (Right).SLDPRT"

		From this example, we can deduce that this is a track drive covering, part number "02", and is used on the right track unit.

----------

IV.) 3D Scans

	If a 3D scan exists for an item or multiple items, it should be placed in a folder named "[SCAN] Scans".

		Example:
			"[TARM-COVR-01] Outer Covering.SLDPRT"
			"[TARM-COVR-01-SCAN] Outer Covering.scn"

		From this example we can deduce this is an outer tool arm covering and its respective 3D scan. The part number, "01" in this example, should also match.

----------

V.) Drawings

	Drawings should follow the same rules as parts. Drawings of assemblies should have "-ASM" at the end the prefix, otherwise, there's no way to differentiate a part drawing from an assembly drawing.

----------

VI.) Part Descriptions

	All parts should have a description to compliment the part. This is a short sentence that describes a part's function, using normal sentence formatting (first letter capitalized, trailing period).
	Unless a part has multiple configurations -- for example, the "25B14" and "25B60" sprockets -- the description should be a global custom property, not a configuration-specific custom property.

----------

VII.) Input-Inc Batch File Renaming Program

	It should be noted that while this program has been extensively tested, it goes without saying that after using this program you should double-check for the desired naming scheme.
	Always keep backups of the CAD before using this program! Its function is not able to be undone. An "undo" function is impossible (or at least, near impossible) to code.